<!--?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?-->
<!DOCTYPE concept PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Concept//EN"
 "C:\Program Files (x86)\DITA-OT1.8.5\dtd\technicalContent\dtd\concept.dtd">
  <concept id="trade" xml:lang="en-us">
  <!--font face = 'Museo Sans For Dell' size = '24' color = 'blue'-->
 <title>Trademarks</title>
 
 <conbody>

 <p>© 2014-2016 Dell Inc. All rights reserved. Reproduction of this material in any manner whatsoever
without the express written permission of Dell Inc. is prohibited. For more information, contact Dell.</p>
 
 
 <p>Trademarks used in this text: Dell™, the DELL logo, Dell Precision™, OptiPlex™, Latitude™, PowerEdge™,
PowerVault™, OpenManage™, EqualLogic™, Dell Compellent™, KACE™, FlexAddress, Dell Networking™,
and Vostro™ are trademarks of Dell Inc. Intel®, Pentium®, Xeon®, Core®, and Celeron® are registered
trademarks of Intel Corporation in the U.S. and other countries. AMD® is a registered trademark and
AMD Opteron™, AMD Phenom™, and AMD Sempron™ are trademarks of Advanced Micro Devices,
Inc. Microsoft®, Windows®, Windows Server®, MS-DOS®, and Windows Vista® are either trademarks or
registered trademarks of Microsoft Corporation in the United States and/or other countries.
</p>




<p>Red Hat®, Red Hat® Enterprise Linux®, the Shadowman logo, and JBoss are trademarks of Red Hat, Inc.,
registered in the U.S. and other countries. Linux® is the registered trademark of Linus Torvalds in the
U.S. and other countries. Novell® is a registered trademark and SUSE™ is a trademark of Novell Inc. in
the United States and other countries. Oracle® is a registered trademark of Oracle Corporation and/or
its affiliates. Citrix®, Xen®, XenServer® and XenMotion® are either registered trademarks or trademarks
of Citrix Systems, Inc. in the United States and/or other countries. VMware®, Virtual SMP®, vMotion®,
vCenter®, and vSphere® are registered trademarks or trademarks of VMware, Inc. in the United States or
other countries.</p>

<p>DISCLAIMER: The OpenStack® Word Mark and OpenStack Logo are either registered trademarks/
service marks or trademarks/service marks of the OpenStack Foundation, in the United States and
other countries, and are used with the OpenStack Foundation's permission. We are not affiliated with,
endorsed or sponsored by the OpenStack Foundation or the OpenStack community.
</p>


<p>Other trademarks and trade names may be used in this publication to refer to either the entities
claiming the marks and names or their products. Dell Inc. disclaims any proprietary interest in
trademarks and trade names other than its own.</p>
 </conbody>

 

 </concept>