<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic id="refrence">
  <title>Reference Architecture Overview</title>
  <body>
  
  <p> Following is the reference architecture for SRIOV deployment in NFV 6.0:</p>
  
 
    <p>Additional Architectural Notes: </p>
	<p>
	<ol>
        <li>	Dell NFV SRIOV architecture provides wireline speed to the virtual appliances running on a Dell Redhat NFV solution 6.0.</li>
        <li>	Dell NFV architecture is powered by Intel®X520 dual port 10G NIC adaptors.</li>
        <li>	Dell NFV SRIOV scripts provides following functionalities in fully automated fashion:
		     <ol>
			 <li>	Enablement of Virtual Functions in Compute nodes
			 <li>Assigning Bandwidth limits to each virtual function</li>
			 <li>Assigning virtual functions to VMs running in OpenStack</li>
			 <li>Creating Physical Function pairs to provide NIC level redundancy</li>
			 <li>bonding</li>
			 </ol>
			 
			 </li>
      </ol>
	  </li>
	   <fig id="fig1">      
      <title> SRIOV with HA Reference Architecture using NFV 6.0</title>

	  <image href="fig1.png" placement="break"><alt> SRIOV with HA Reference Architecture using NFV 6.0</alt></image>
      </fig>
	  </p>
	  <p>Additional Hardware Notes: </p>
	  <p>
	  <ol>
        <li>	In addition to standard NFV 6.0 hardware, SRIOV enablement requires additional hardware,
		i.e. Intel X520, SFP, QSFP connectors, and fiber breakout cables, details can be found in next sections.</li>
        <li>	In addition to default networks of NFV 6.0, SRIOV enablement will require additional networks (VLANs) 
		to communicate between physical functions and physical switch. Please refer to network diagram in next section.</li>
        <li>	SRIOV also requires one external network that can communicate to external datacenter. Detailed network topology is provided in next section.
		     </li>
      </ol>
	  </p>
	  </body>
	  </topic>