<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic id="topic_gfg_fkz_xp">
  <title>Trademarks</title>
  <body>
    <p>&#169; 2014-2016 <keyword keyref="company_name_long"/> All rights reserved. Reproduction of this material in any manner
      whatsoever without the express written permission of <keyword keyref="company_name_long"/> is prohibited. For more
      information, contact <keyword keyref="company_name_short"/>.</p>
    <p>Trademarks used in this text: <tm trademark="Dell" tmtype="tm">Dell</tm>, the DELL logo, <tm
        trademark="PowerEdge" tmtype="tm">PowerEdge</tm>, and <tm trademark="Dell Networking"
          tmtype="tm">Dell Networking</tm> are trademarks of <keyword keyref="company_name_long"/> <tm trademark="Intel" tmtype="reg">Intel</tm> and <tm trademark="Xeon" tmtype="reg">Xeon</tm> are registered trademarks of Intel Corporation in the U.S. and other countries. <tm trademark="Microsoft"
        tmtype="reg">Microsoft</tm> and <tm trademark="Windows" tmtype="reg">Windows</tm> are
      registered trademarks of Microsoft Corporation in the United States and/or other
      countries.</p>
    <p><tm trademark="Red Hat" tmtype="reg">Red Hat</tm>, Red Hat <tm trademark="Enterprise Linux"
        tmtype="reg">Enterprise Linux</tm>, and Ceph are trademarks or registered trademarks of Red
      Hat, Inc., registered in the U.S. and other countries. <tm trademark="Linux" tmtype="reg"
        >Linux</tm> is the registered trademark of Linus Torvalds in the U.S. and other countries.
        <tm trademark="Oracle" tmtype="reg">Oracle</tm> and <tm trademark="Java" tmtype="reg"
        >Java</tm> are registered trademarks of Oracle Corporation and/or its affiliates.</p>
    <p>DISCLAIMER: The <tm trademark="OpenStack" tmtype="reg">OpenStack</tm> Word Mark and OpenStack
      Logo are either registered trademarks/service marks or trademarks/service marks of the
      OpenStack Foundation, in the United States and other countries, and are used with the
      OpenStack Foundation's permission. We are not affiliated with, endorsed or sponsored by the
      OpenStack Foundation or the OpenStack community.</p>
    <p>The <tm trademark="Midokura" tmtype="reg">Midokura</tm> name and logo, as well as the <tm
        trademark="MidoNet" tmtype="reg">MidoNet</tm> name and logo, are registered trademarks of
      Midokura SARL.</p>
    <p>Other trademarks and trade names may be used in this publication to refer to either the
      entities claiming the marks and names or their products. <keyword keyref="company_name_long"/> disclaims any proprietary
      interest in trademarks and trade names other than its own.</p>
  </body>
</topic>